Finding Aid for Nu Sigma Nu, Alpha Chapter. (University of Michigan) records, 1882-1999
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Publications
  - Nu Sigma Nu Bulletins (Hardcover) (Box 6)
    - Nu Sigma Nu Bulletin (Nineteenth Chapter Series 1928-1929) (Box 7)
    - Nu Sigma Nu Bulletin (Twentieth Chapter Series 1929-1930) (Box 7)
    - Nu Sigma Nu Bulletin (Twenty-First Chapter Series 1930-1931) (Box 7)
    - Nu Sigma Nu Bulletin (Twenty-Second Chapter Series 1931-1932) (Box 7)
    - Nu Sigma Nu Bulletin (Twenty-Third Chapter Series 1932-1933) (Box 7)
    - Nu Sigma Nu Bulletin (Twenty-Fourth Chapter Series 1933-1934) (Box 8)
    - Nu Sigma Nu Bulletin (Twenty-Fifth Chapter Series 1934-1935) (Box 8)
    - The Nu Sigma Nu Bulletin (Volume XXVI, 1935-1937) (Box 8)
    - The Nu Sigma Nu Bulletin (Volume XXVII, 1937-1938) (Box 8)
    - The Nu Sigma Nu Bulletin (Volume XXX, 1940-1941) (Box 8)
    - The Nu Sigma Nu Bulletin (Volume XXXI, 1941-1942) (Box 8)
    - The Nu Sigma Nu Bulletin (Volume XXXII, 1942-1943) (Box 8)
    - The Nu Sigma Nu Bulletin (Volume XXXIII, 1943-1944) (Box 8)
    - The Nu Sigma Nu Bulletin (Volume XXXV, 1945-1946) (Box 8)
    - The Nu Sigma Nu Bulletin (Volume XXXVII, 1947-1948) (Box 8)